const beginnerMediumQuestions = [
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'Which of these is not a musical term?',
    answers: ['Sharp', 'Flat', 'Point'],
    correct: 'Point',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'Which string has the highest tone?',
    answers: ['A', 'G', 'B'],
    correct: 'B',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'Where is the bridge on a guitar?',
    answers: [
      'At the top of the neck',
      'On the body',
      'On the underside of the guitar',
    ],
    correct: 'On the body',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'What note sounds the most “bright”?',
    answers: ['Major', 'Minor', 'Grande'],
    correct: 'Major',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: 'Which “clef” is used for guitar?',
    answers: ['Treble', 'Bass', 'Hue'],
    correct: 'Treble',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'What is the third string from the top of a guitar?',
    answers: ['G', 'D', 'A'],
    correct: 'D',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: 'How many frets are held down for a “D” chord?',
    answers: ['3', '4', '5'],
    correct: '3',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: 'What is a rest?',
    answers: ['A nap', 'A pause in music theory', 'A drawn out note'],
    correct: 'A pause in music theory',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: 'What is a chord?',
    answers: [
      'A music symbol',
      'A type of note',
      'A series of notes played in unison',
    ],
    correct: 'A series of notes played in unison',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: 'Which note is held for longer?',
    answers: ['A whole note', 'A quarter note', 'A half note'],
    correct: 'A whole note',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: 'What is a riff?',
    answers: [
      'A repeated chord progression or refrain',
      'A type of chord',
      'A part of the guitar by the neck',
    ],
    correct: 'A repeated chord progression or refrain',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
]

export { beginnerMediumQuestions }
